imvbox.com 2019-04-21

# Privacy Policy | IMVBox | Watch Iranian Movies & Documentaries Online

This Privacy Policy describes how IMVBox collects and process personal information about you, how IMVBox uses and protect this information, and your rights in relation to this information.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using IMVBox, you agree to this Privacy Policy Our Cookies Policy and Terms of Use.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

IMVBox will collect Personal Information about you from a variety of sources, including information We collect from you directly, information We automatically collect from your use of the Services, and information we collect about you from other sources, described below.

\- Information IMVbox collect directly from you:

Registration information

When you create an account, you provide IMVBox with certain Personal information, such as email address, password and how did you hear about us;

Profile information

You may also complete a profile, which may include your full name and country. Please note that your profile information can be visible to other users of Our Services;

Payment information

We collect your payment information when you subscribe to plus memberships;

Other information

You may choose to provide IMVBox with certain information when you use IMVBox Invite a Friend referral program, fill out a form, submit a request, respond to a survey, submit ratings and reviews and participate in promotions.

-Information We automatically collect from your use of the Services:

Usage information

We automatically collect information about how you use IMVBox.com, such as pages you view, content you view or saved to watch later, subtitles options and searches you make;

Device information

We may collect certain technical information about your device, such as your IP Address, geolocation information (city and country), your browser type, language, your operating system and application version, device types, device model and manufacturer, device identifier and your device operating system type and version;

Transactional information

We automatically collect certain information about your transactions on the Services such as amount charged, date and time; and

Cookies and similar technologies

As further described in our [Cookies Policy](https://www.imvbox.com/cookies-policy), We and Our partners automatically collect information from cookies and similar technologies (such as cookies IDs and settings) to recognize you, track your behavior on the Services and your device, and to serve you with tailored advertisements. For more information on how We use cookies and how you can manage them, please visit Our [Cookies Policy](https://www.imvbox.com/cookies-policy).

-Information We collect from other sources:

Registration through third parties

If you don’t feel like creating an account from scratch, We provide you with the option to sign in to an account you already have with another service provider (such as Facebook). The third-party service may send us information such as your name, email address, date of birth, geographic location, interest, profile picture, list of friends and any other information you have made available on these third-party services. This information is controlled by the third-party service or as authorized by you via your privacy settings at the third-party service;

Social media third parties

Some of IMVBox Services allow you to post information through social media sites, plugins or other applications. Don’t forget this information is public on Our Services and depending on your privacy settings, may also become public on the internet. We may also further use such public information you share for various reasons such as improving Our Services and providing you with relevant content. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. Please refer to those third-party privacy policies and terms of use to learn more about their privacy practices, as We don’t control these; and

Other sources

We may receive additional information about you from third-party service providers and/or partners, such as demographic data, your activities on and off Our Services through partnerships and Our third party advertisers.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

The information IMVBox collect from you ensures you can use Our Services in a safe environment. Because of that, IMVBox may use your information for the following purposes:

Services

We may use your information to: enable you to access and use the Services, authenticate your identity when you log in to Our Services, personalize or otherwise customise your experience by, for example, providing you with content based on your search and preferences, determine your general geographic location to personalize Our Services, to recommend content and determine whether the content you have requested is available in your region, process your payment for the Services through third party service providers, and manage the accounts you hold with IMVBox;

Advertising

IMVBox, and Our third-party advertisers, use your Personal Information in order to serve you with advertisements that may interest you (you can find below more information about Our third-party advertisers);

Marketing

IMVBox uses your information to send you promotional messages, newsletters, marketing and other information that may be of interest to you based on your preferences, including information about Our affiliates and partners campaigns and services. We, and Our third-party business partners, also use your Personal Information, on and off Our Services, to serve you with advertisements of Our Services. From time to time, IMVBox, and our third-party service providers and/or business partners, may also use your information to administrate surveys, contests, referral programs or other promotional activities or events managed by IMVBox, Our affiliates and/or Our partners if you consent;

Communication

IMVBox use your information to contact you to maintain Our Services and to respond and resolve your support requests, questions and issues;

Security

IMVBox use your information if We think it is necessary to investigate and prevent security issues and abuse, protect Our Trademarks and enforce Our Terms of Use;

Research and services improvement

In an effort to provide you with the best Services, We may use your information to conduct research for further development of the Services;

Legal

IMVBox may use your information to comply with legal obligations to which We are subject and cooperate with regulators and law enforcement bodies.

**HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION**

IMVBox may share your Personal Information with third parties under the following circumstances:

With your consent

We may share your information, if you consent, after letting you know what information will be shared and with whom and why;

Service providers

We share your Personal Information with Our service providers that perform business services and/or operations on Our behalf. For example, We may partner with other companies to process secure payments, provide authentication services, fulfill orders, perform analytics, send newsletters and marketing emails, administer Our promotions, contests, and surveys, and support email and messaging services;

Business partners

We may share your Personal Information with Our business partners to perform business services upon the selected service or plan and/or your request. For example, We may partner with other companies to provide content, streaming and content delivery services, and targeted advertising services;

Law enforcement agencies, courts, regulators and government authorities

We may share your Personal Information with these parties where We believe this is necessary to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation, or otherwise to protect Our rights or the rights of any third party; and

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS**

IMVBox permit advertisements to be delivered to you by third-party advertisers (also called ad networks or network advertisers). These third party advertisers may use Personal Information (such as- cookies, platform device identifiers, software agents, and IP address), in order to deliver targeted advertisements, measure their effectiveness, and to understand the usage and visitation of IMVBox Services and the other applications and websites tracked by these companies. We do not have access to or control over cookies, platform device identifiers, software agents, or other technologies that they may use. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party advertisers. For more information about how the online advertising industry uses information it collects to provide you with a tailored advertisement, and to control whether you want to receive those relevant advertisement from Our third-party advertisers, please review the information at the following links: [The Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/); and [Your Ad Choices](https://youradchoices.com/).

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

Our Services may contain links to other third-party websites. IMVBox encourage you to be aware of these other third-party websites and their privacy statements, as We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third-party sites.

**YOUR CHOICES AND YOUR RIGHTS OVER YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Your choices

You may in some cases have the option to decline to provide Us information. However, your choice to not provide information may impact your use of certain features or services. Please find below some choices you have over your Personal Information:

-Account

You can change information about your account by accessing your Account and modifying the information. You are not required to provide any information to Us that is unnecessary to provide the Services.

-Marketing communication

You can unsubscribe or opt-out of receiving marketing communications from Us by using the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of an automatic email or by contacting US  at [support@imvbox.com](mailto:support@imvbox.com). Please note that even if you opt-out of receiving marketing communication, We may continue to send you non-marketing emails and other types of communications, as permitted by law, such as response to your support requests, or service email relating to your account.

-Cookies

You may control the use of cookies at the browser level. If you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on IMVBox Services. For more information on how we use cookies and how you can manage them please see Our[ Cookie Policy](https://www.imvbox.com/cookies-policy).

Your rights

Subject to local law, you may have certain rights regarding information that IMVBox has collected and that is related to you. We encourage you to Contact Us to update or correct your information if it changes or if you believe that any information that We have collected about you is inaccurate.

Please note that IMVBox will likely require additional information from you in order to honor your requests.

If you would like to discuss or exercise such rights, send Us at [support@imvbox.com](mailto:support@imvbox.com)

Rights applicable to EU users

-Data Transfer

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from E.U. or U.S. law, please note that your Personal Information may need to be processed in countries where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in your home country.

-Legal basis for processing your Personal Information

If you are visiting from the European Union, We must have a legal basis to process your Personal Information. There are different legal bases that IMVBox relies on to use your Personal Information, namely:

-Performance of a contract:

The use of your information may be necessary to perform the terms and conditions or other contractual obligations and policies under which We provide our Services to you;

-Consent

We will rely on your consent to use (i) technical information such as cookie and similar technologies; and (ii) your information for marketing and advertising purposes. You may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting Us using the information at the end of this Privacy Policy or by following an unsubscribe link in any marketing communication you receive from IMVBox.

-Legitimate interests

We use your Personal Information for Our legitimate interests to improve our Services, security purposes, and to share information with Our affiliates for internal administration. In such circumstances it is for Us to ensure that these interests are not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms; and

-Legal obligation and public interest

In some cases, We may also have a legal obligation to collect your Personal Information, or may otherwise need your Personal Information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

-Your Choices under EU law

If you are visiting from the European Economic Area, you may have certain rights, in accordance with the applicable local law and limitations, including the right to access your Personal Information; to rectify the information We hold about you; to erase your Personal Information; to restrict our use of your Personal Information; to object to our use of your Personal Information; and to receive your Personal Information in a usable electronic format and transmit it to a third party (right to data portability). Contact us at [support@imvbox.com](mailto:support@imvbox.com).

If you believe that your data protection rights may have been breached, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority in the country of your habitual residence, place of work or of the potential breach, or to seek a remedy through the courts. The supervisory authority in the UK is the Information Commissioner's Office, whose website at [ico.org.uk](https://ico.org.uk/) provides information on how you can lodge a complaint.

**SECURITY**

IMVBox care about the security of your Personal Information. We implement technical and organizational measures to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk to the Personal Information We process. These measures are aimed at ensuring the on-going integrity and confidentiality of your Personal Information. However, no company can guarantee that data may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of Our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. We need your help too: it is your responsibility to make sure that your Personal Information is accurate and that your password is unique, secure and not shared with third parties.

**RETENTION**

IMVBox will keep your Personal Information for as long as We have a relationship with you. We will only retain your Personal Information after this time if We are required to do so to comply with the local law, or if there are outstanding claims or complaints that will reasonably require your Personal Information to be retained.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 Children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please; contact us at [support@imvbox.com](mailto:support@imvbox.com). If we discover that a Children under the age of 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

From time to time, as Our Services evolve, we may modify or update this privacy policy.

The most current version will govern Our use of your Personal Information and will always be available at [imvbox.com/privacy-policy](https://www.imvbox.com/privacy-policy). If We make changes that We think will have a substantial impact on your rights, We will notify you. Otherwise, you agree to accept any changes or updates to this privacy policy by continuing to use Our Services.

**CONTACT US**

If you still have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via [support@imvbox.com](mailto:support@imvbox.com); or you can send us a physical mail at:

Office 441

22 Notting Hill Gate

London, England

W11 3JE

Thank you for using IMVBox.com

Last Updated: May 25, 2018
